<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FatLogger</string>
    <string name="app_title">FatLogger</string>
    <string name="app_subtitle">Food Encyclopedia</string>
    <string name="title_activity_result">Results</string>
    <string name="loading_text">Processing results</string>
    <string name="food_image_description">Food Image</string>
    <string name="title_activity_diary">Diary</string>
    <string name="title_diary">Diary</string>
    <string name="title_progress">Progress</string>
    <string name="date_select">Today </string>
    <string name="title_activity_info">About Developers</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "FatLogger, an advanced Android application, has been developed to cater to the needs of users seeking precise nutritional information regarding their meals. By leveraging its intuitive interface, users can effortlessly capture food photos, subsequently accessing a wealth of comprehensive nutritional data. The app also provides a convenient feature for users to save their food records within a dedicated diary, enabling them to maintain a meticulous log of their dietary choices. Furthermore, FatLogger offers users a visualized analysis of their eating habits, empowering them with valuable insights to make informed decisions about their nutrition.\n\n"
        "The image recognition functionality within FatLogger is implemented through a highly effective convolutional neural network (CNN). Renowned for its ability to accurately classify visual data, the CNN employed in FatLogger ensures reliable identification and analysis of food images. The development of this robust model is underpinned by the powerful TensorFlow framework, renowned for its capabilities in deep learning. The developers invested substantial efforts into training the CNN, utilizing an extensive dataset comprising over 100,000 images. As a result, FatLogger exhibits superior accuracy and efficiency in recognizing and classifying various food items.\n\n"
        "The application boasts an extensive and diverse list of supported foods, encompassing a wide range of culinary options. Users can conveniently access nutritional information for popular items such as hamburgers, strawberries, pancakes, bread, hotdogs, doughnuts, spaghetti, crackers, pizza, milk, cucumbers, lasagna, broccoli, boiled eggs, muffins, mangoes, shrimp, lettuce, avocados, fried eggs, steaks, burritos, grapes, watermelons, French fries, nachos, macaroni, apples, English muffins, dumplings, tomatoes, bacon, baked potatoes, chocolates, rice, popcorn, fried chicken, tacos, oranges, chili, celery, croissants, peaches, coffee, bananas, corn, ice cream, mashed potatoes, and chips.\n\n"
        "It is worth noting that the development of FatLogger was undertaken as part of the Open Source project for the Master of Science in Software Engineering program at Nankai University. The application was meticulously crafted by a talented team of developers, including Samrand Hassan (Student ID: 2120226103, Email: 2120226103@mail.nankai.edu.cn), Mashkhal Abdalwahid Sidiq (Student ID: 2120226099, Email: 2120226099@mail.nankai.edu.cn), Aras Aziz Aram (Student ID: 2120226102, Email: 2120226102@mail.nankai.edu.cn), Brwa Hamadameen Faiq (Student ID: 2120226101, Email: brwa.hamadameen@gmail.com), Hawzheen Mohammed Ali (Student ID: 2120226104, Email: hawzheen.ali11@gmail.com) and Ngin Hama Salih Ahmed (Student ID: 2120226100, Email: 2120226100@mail.nankai.edu.cn). Their collective expertise and dedication have resulted in the creation of a remarkable application that meets the rigorous standards of academic and professional excellence.\n\n"
        "By amalgamating cutting-edge technology, comprehensive nutritional analysis, and user-centric design, FatLogger emerges as a significant contribution to the field of mobile applications. It not only satisfies the informational needs of users but also empowers individuals to cultivate healthier eating habits through informed decision-making. The meticulous attention to detail exhibited by the development team underscores their commitment to providing users with a seamless and enriching experience.\n\n"    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
